Gross, James A. Additional Arbitration Files 5959
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
James A. Gross Additional Arbitration Files
1978-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gross, James A.
5959
12 cubic feet
12 linear ft.
Files, records (documents).
3126428
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 22, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Professor Gross teaches Labor Law, Labor Arbitration, and a course entitled Values, Rights and Justice in Economics, Law, and Industrial Relations. He received his B.S. from LaSalle College, M.A. from Temple University, and Ph.D. from University of Wisconsin.
Professor Gross is a member of National Academy of Arbitrators and on the labor arbitration panels of the American Arbitration Association, Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service and New York State Public Employment Relations Board, as well as being a panelist named in several contracts.[www.ilr.cornell.edu/directory/jag28/biography.htm]
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4057 P: James A. Gross NLRB Photographs /4124: James A. Gross Papers, Additional NLRB Research Files /4166: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Files /4186: James A. Gross Additional Research Files /4190: James A. Gross Additional Research Files 5697: James A. Gross Arbitration Files 5959: James A. Gross Additional Arbitration Files /4079: James A. Gross Additional Files
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Gross, James A.,1933-
3126428
- Addison Central School District Amalgamated Meatcutters and Stop & Shop. (Box 1)
  - Addison Central School District [folder 1 of 3], 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    3020-A
  - Addison Central School District [folder 2 of 3], 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Addison Central School District (3020-a), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Albany State Policy and PBA, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Addison Central School District [folder 3 of 3], 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Police Benevolent Association of the New York State Police, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alden Central School, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    AAA #15-390-0005-89
  - Alden Central School (AAA 15 390 0005 89), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alice Hyde Hospital, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    AAA #15-300-0483-19 LRC
  - Alice Hyde Hospital (AAA 15 300 0483 91 LRC), 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allied Chemical, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    FMCS #80K-20624
  - Allied Chemical 80k-20624, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Can Company [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    FMCS #85K-19020
  - American Can Company (FMCS 85K19020), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Can Company FMCS 80K/17669, 1965-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Can Company [folder 2 of 2], 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Stop and Shop, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Can Company [folder 1 of 3], 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    FMCS #80K-17669
  - American Can Company [folder 2 of 3], 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Can Company [folder 3 of 3], 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Stop & Shop, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Amsterdam Printing Buffalo Board of Education. (Box 2)
  - Amsterdam Printing and Litho Corporation (AAA 15 300 0514 87), 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Amsterdam Printing and Litho Corporation, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    AAA #15-300-0514-87
  - Armstrong Cork Co. (3/79), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Armstrong Cork (12/74), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Armstrong Cork, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Armstrong Cork, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Armstrong World Industries, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    FMCS #84K-19626
  - Auburn Correctional Facility, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    PERB #85-42-D
  - Armstrong World Ind. Inc. (FMCS 84k/19626), 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Auburn Memorial Hospital, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    AAA #15-30-0459-83
  - Auburn Correctional Facility (Sgt. Gordon Hetherington) PERB 85-42-D), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - AVX Ceramics [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - AVX Ceramics [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Auburn Memorial Hosp. (AAA 15-30-0459-83), 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Binghamton City School District [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    AAA #15-390-0013-87
  - Avex Ceramics Corp., 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Binghamton City School District [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Brockport Faculty Student Association, SUNY (Box 2, Folder 11)
    FMCS #92-12741
  - Brooktondale Division of Youth, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    MacCormick Secure Center. AAA #15-E670-0063-86
  - Binghamton City School District (AAA 15 390 0013 87), 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Buffalo Board of Education, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    PERB #A85-241
  - Buffalo Board of Education, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Brockport Fac./Stud. Assoc., Suny (FMCS 92-12741), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Brooktondale Division of Youth (MacCormick Secure Center) (AAA 15 E670 0063 86, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Buffalo Board of Education (Perb A85-241), 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Educ. 5/79, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Buffalo Board of Education Cargill. (Box 3)
  - Buffalo Board of Education, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    PERB #A83-47
  - Buffalo Board of Education, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    PERB #A79-144
  - Buffalo Board of Education, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    PERB #88-447
  - Buffalo Board of Education, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    X-Country Coach Position. PERB # A88-109
  - Buffalo Board of Education, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Buffalo Teachers Federation.
  - Buffalo Courier Express [folder 1 of 3], 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    AAA #15-30-0676-81
  - Buffalo Courier Express [folder 2 of 3], 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo Courier Express [folder 3 of 3], 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Buffalo Firefighters Association, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    PERB #A87-102
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Educ. (A83-47), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Buffalo Police Benevolent Association, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    PERB #A88-040
  - Camden Central School District, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    AAA #15-390-0402-87
  - Cargill and IAM Local Union 1607, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Education A79-144, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Buffalo Board of Education (PERB 88-447), 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Buffalo Board of Education (PERB A88-109) (X Country Coach Position), 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Buffalo Bd. Of Educ. Buffalo Teachers Fed., 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Buffalo Courier Express, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Buffalo Courier Express (AAA 15 30 0676 81), 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo Firefighters Association (PERB A87-102), 1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Buffalo Police Benevolent Assn./ City of Buffalo (Perb A88-040), 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Camden Central School District (AAA 15 390 0402 87), 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Cargill, Inc. and IAM Union 1607, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Carrier Climax Manufacturing. (Box 4)
  - Carrier Corporation (C7359 and C7346), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Cayuga County and CSEA (AAA 15 390 0107 89), 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Central New York Psychiatric Center (Perb Case 85-21-D) (James Magnanti), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Champion International Corporation (FMCS 86K/29719), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Charles Driscoll Masonry (FMCS 83K15217), 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Chenango Valley Teachers Association (AAA 15 390 0107 85), 1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Chesapeake Corporation (AAA 15 300 0135 86), 1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Pneumatic Tool Company and I.A.M., 1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - City of Corning and Crystal City Police Benv. Assoc. (AAA 15 390 0071 89), 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - City of Lockport (AAA 15 39 0378 80), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - City of Oswego (AAA 15 390 0672 84), 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Climax Manufacturing Co. (AAA 15 300 0520 86), 1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Clinton Central School (AAA 15 390 0024 88), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Clinton Central School Elmira PBA. (Box 5)
  - Corning-Painted Post Area School District and CSEA, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Crown Zellerbach, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - DCASMA (FMCS 84K/21963), 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - CSEA and Field Staff Association (AAA 15 300 0555 85, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - E. Syracuse Minoa School District (AAA 15 390 0329 86), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Elmira, City of (Perb A86-101), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Elmira City School District (AAA 15 390 0043 86), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Elmira City School District, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Elmira PBA/ City of Elmira (AAA 15 390, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Franklin Central School Jamestown Firefighters Association. (Box 6)
  - Franklin Central School (AAA 15 390 0643 85), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Frontier School District (AAA 15 390 0596 87), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Gloversville Teachers Association (AAA 15 390 0401 88), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Gowanda School District (AAA 15 390 0379 86), 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Griffith Institute School (AAA 15 390 0358 89), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Hammermill Papers Group (FMCS 87k/12159), 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Health Science Center at Syracuse (AAA 15 300 0124 89), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Herkimer County Boces (AAA 15 390 0218 86), 1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Hoffman Air and Filtration Systems (FMCS 90-22409), 1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Horseheads School District (AAA 15 390 0304 87), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Horseheads School District (AAA 15 390 0309 85), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Hussmann Corporation, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Ingersoll Rand Co. FMCS 81k-21771, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - International Salt Company - (AAA 15 300 0441 86), 1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Ithaca City School District (AAA 15 390 0364 90Kmz), 1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Jamestown Fire Fighters Association (PERB A87-124), 1983-1987 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Jasper School District Morrison Knudsen Company. (Box 7)
  - Jasper School District (AAA 15 390 0117 86), 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Kennedy Valve (FMCS 84 K/21124, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Label Processing Corp., 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Linden Chemicals and Plastics Corp. (FMCS 86k/08172), 1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Lipe Corporation (FMCS 89-01064), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 15 39 0668 77, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Marcellus School District (AAA 15 390 0644 87), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Marcellus School District (AAA 15 390 0369 87), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Massena Memorial Hospital/CSEA, Inc. (AAA 15 30 0204 84), 1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Mohawk Valley Community College/MVCC (AAA 15 390 0286 88), 1988 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Monarch Machine Tool Co. (FMCS 87-24554), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Monarch Machine Tool Co. (FMCS 83k/11774), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Monroe Community Hospital (FMCS 84k/01587), 1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Morrison-Knudsen Company, Inc. (FMCS 87k/12189), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Monsanto Company NYS United Teachers. (Box 8)
  - Monsanto Company (FMCS 86k/03562), 1986 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - New York Air Brake (AAA 15 300 0369 89), 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - New York Air Brake Co. (FMCS 82k/12028), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - New York Air Brake (AAA 15 300 0352 87), 1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Niagara Frontier Transp. Authority (PERB Case A90-385), 1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - New York Telephone (NYT A-89-155; CWA 1-89-189; 9039.0247, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - New York Telephone (Case A-88-257), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - New York Telephone (Case Nos., A-89-61, A-89-62, A-89-76 and A-89-107; CWA Case 1-89-177(493), 1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - New York Telephone (A-87-466), 1987 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - New York Telephone/CWA (A-87-4 and A-87-5), 1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - New York State United Teachers (AAA 15 300 0076 85), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Newton Falls Paper Mill Rochester Telephone. (Box 9)
  - Newton Falls Paper Mill (AAA 15 300 0011 86), 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Newton Falls Paper Mill (AAA 15 30 0580 83), 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Northland, A. Scott Fetzer Co. (AAA 15 300 0535 84), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Nynex Corporation (Gr. 1123-87-0014E; Your File No. 9039.0180; Co. A-87-26, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Nynex and CWA (A-88-3), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Odessa Montour School (AAA 15 E390 0262 89), 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Oswego County and CSEA (Perb A-88-323) (Joyce Richman), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Pall Trinity Micro Corp. AAA 15 30 0346 80, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Pioneer Central School (15 390 0370 89), 1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Plaza Nursing Home (AAA 15 30 0422 83), 1983 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Rathbone Corp. AAA 1130-1293-81, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Revere Copper Products (FMCS 85k/23876), 1985 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Rochester Telephone 9039.0204, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Rochester Telephone Shepard Niles. (Box 10)
  - Rochester Telephone Corp. (9039.0205 - G. Brugger), 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Rochester Telephone (Attorneys' Files 9039.0006) Single Day Vacation, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Rochester Telephone Co./CWA 1-89-30, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Rochester Telephone Co. (00-793-797-83), 1983 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Rollway Bearing (AAA 15 30 0599 83), 1983 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Schoeller Technical Press (AAA 15 300 0413 87), 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Schrader-Bellows (FMCS 85K00434), 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Schuyler Chemung Tioga Boces (AAA 15 390 0323 88), 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Shepard Niles Crane and Hoist Corp. (FMCS 85K/16840), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Shepard Niles Crane and Hoist Corp. (FMCS 85K/21602), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Shepard Niles Crane and Hoist Corporation (FMCS 85K/09120), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- St. Elizabeth Hospital Victory Markets. (Box 11)
  - St. Elizabeth Hospital 15 30 0038 80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Syracuse China Corp. (AAA 15 30 0438 83), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Syracuse Fire Fighters and City of Syracuse, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Syracuse PBA and City of Syracuse, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Syracuse Teachers Assoc. (Machida) (AAA 15 390 0181 86), 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Syracuse University (AAA 15 30 0121 84), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Thornier-Sidney Press, Inc. (AAA 15 300 0274 88), 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Utica City School District (AAA 15 390 058 86), 1986 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Utica City School District (AAA 15 390 0198 86), 1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Victory Markets (FMCS 91-20286), 1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- W. Genessee School District Worthington Group. (Box 12)
  - West Genesee School District (AAA 15 390 0180 88), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Westinghouse Broadcasting Co. and I.B.E.W., 1970 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Wheatland Chili Central School (AAA 15 390 0593 86), 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - WNYT-TV, Viacom Broadcasting, Inc./NABET (AAA 15 300 0611 84), 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Worthington Group (McGraw Edison Co.) AAA 15 30 0368 81, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Worthington Group (McGraw Edison Co.) AAA 15 30 0368 81, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)